=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 15=
So?
Think it through carefully.
Mr. Fan,
give me a straight answer.
How much of this
is based on Chenxing's
value in your eyes,
and how much is because of He Han?
Of course, it's because of Chenxing.
I am investing in Chenxing.
What I value is Chenxing's future.
Then, what if
He Han is not part of that future?
Weren't you just...
It's such a pity
that you are not together.
Right now, He Han
is a freelance creator.
He is not tied to any company.
Doesn't it mean
that he is just
waiting to return to Chenxing?
He Han and I
are just old friends who
look out for each other.
I hope those who invest in Chenxing
value Chenxing and me,
not a bundled deal with He Han.
I understand.
I know
you have integrity.
As for me,
what I value is you
and your Chenxing.
As for He Han,
he is just an added bonus.
How do you prove that?
In business,
money is proof.
I won't change the number here.
That should be proof enough, right?
Remove the parts related
to He Han in the contract.
We can talk another time.
No need.
We can do it now.
I have prepared
both options.
You can take them back and review them.
That is fine.
Then, over the next couple of days,
let's get it signed as
soon as possible, alright?
I may not be that fast.
The sooner, the better.
I need to go in now.
Instant noodles?
Careful. It's hot.
Hey,
where are you working now?
This is your alt account, right?
Bro,
join our guild.
Let's play together.
Come here.
What?
I said come here.
So Lin Zhanqiao still
ended up pushing you around.
What happened?
Got new people and stopped valuing you?
To be fair,
you do look quite sharp now.
That's you, darn it.
Watch your words, Mr. Gu Yan.
Don't be sarcastic or snide here.
No, you just want to dress like this,
but don't want to be judged and ranked.
But let me tell you,
once you dress like this,
you will be judged and ranked.
Because you are already in that system.
It feels uncomfortable to wear,
so I won't wear it.
If it's uncomfortable,
then just don't wear it.
That is right.
I won't wear it.
You are really cutting it?
With this one snip,
a thousand is gone.
Would he not feel the loss?
Help me cut it, too.
You said it.
No compensation.
Cut it.
But we are not paying for it.
You said it.
This feels great. I...
These scissors are sharp. Just cut it.
If you keep cutting like this,
will he not make you pay for it?
Gu Yan's award.
He is not here, and neither are you,
so I accepted it on your behalf.
So?
All settled?
I got Mr. Fan,
but I lost Gu Yan.
That won't happen.
He is just throwing a bit of a tantrum.
He is easy to calm down.
Just explain things clearly to him.
Think back to when the two of us
decided to build Chenxing together.
Up until now,
it has only been five or six years.
If I sign this paper,
it will all be over.
Mr. Fan takes 70 percent,
and I keep 30 percent.
I may become an employee,
but at least,
Chenxing's name will still be there.
That makes me feel a little better.
No matter what,
it's still better than losing
the whole company, right?
If you don't want to sell it,
then don't sell it.
There will always be
a way to keep going.
Who are you?
You are Lin Zhanqiao. Come on.
Listen,
smash this trophy right now.
Let it all out.
Smash it. Smash it hard.
Just like you smashed
our trophy back then.
Smash it hard.
I didn't do that on purpose back then.
Then, do it on purpose now.
Is your broken trophy still around?
Of course.
Mr. Fan said he would get us a new one.
I said no.
A trophy full of scars is a real trophy,
right?
Smash it.
If you won't, I'll do it for you.
Why are you so determined
to make me smash it?
Then, I'll smash it.
If you won't, I'll.
Or are you afraid Gu Yan will get mad?
Not at all.
He is very emotionally stable.
Calm and composed.
At most, when he is upset,
he just leaves for a while.
At least, from now on,
I won't have to worry
that at any time, anywhere,
I may have to go
clean up someone's mess.
Are you saying that
because you miss me?
Right?
The show is over for today, okay?
Your acting was very obvious today.
Was it?
Of course.
There was so much
applause from the audience.
That means I was right.
That was because
I led the applause, okay?
You led the applause?
Yes.
Why didn't you
stand up and lead it for us?
A few men beside you had fallen asleep.
You should go back first.
They have plans tonight.
I don't know when they will be back.
I am not in a hurry.
I have nowhere to go anyway.
Don't you develop so many hotels?
You are always pointing at some hotel
and saying you built it,
and they still owe you tens of millions.
Why not find a hotel now,
take a bath,
drink some warm milk,
and get a good sleep?
I'll stay another half hour.
Go on with your work.
I won't bother you.
I think
staying in this room
feels especially comfortable.
Do you know why?
No.
Because your boss
has excellent taste in decor.
You know how many people spend a fortune
making their homes look like palaces,
only for them to feel uncomfortable?
That is just paying to suffer.
Look at you,
and your boss's female friend, Zhou Mei.
Why do you both like living here?
That makes sense.
Are you talking to me about this
because you really
have no other girlfriends to ask out?
Asking out other girlfriends right now
would only upset me.
What I need right now is peace.
She's back.
Ms. Lin.
Ms. Lin...
Qian Jingjing has been discharged.
She is finally out.
I don't plan to get
married anymore either.
Before the wedding,
being able to see a person clearly
is heaven's arrangement.
It's a good thing.
Hasn't Zhangzhu always hoped
you wouldn't get married again?
As long as you have handled it
and thought it through.
But he hasn't handled it.
It's about the house.
That house
was originally
renovated for the wedding.
But since the wedding is off,
Qian Jingjing got so angry
that she smashed the whole place.
What do you mean by the whole place?
She really smashed everything.
Look at these photos.
Everything is shattered.
Wasn't Qian Jingjing's bone fractured?
How could she still
smash things so badly?
It's a house of 200-300 square meters.
We must call the police. This is
the destruction of
someone else's property.
Once she is out of the hospital,
she should spend
some time at the police station.
Forget it.
I build houses and do renovations.
If it's smashed,
I'll just make a new one.
The main thing is that no one gets hurt.
Ms. Lin, I just think
Zhangzhu will still be
staying here for a while.
If... I mean,
if Qian Jingjing comes here
to cause trouble
and tries to smash your place,
you must protect the people first.
If anything gets broken,
I'll replace it for you.
Until this matter is settled,
I'll send people here
every day to stand guard.
First, there is no need to
have someone on duty.
She probably won't hurt anyone.
At most, she will just make a scene.
Besides, you are here
to clean things up.
Second,
she probably won't go after Zhangzhu.
After all,
the reason you called off the wedding
has nothing to do with her.
Ms. Lin, you really see things clearly.
You are the most insightful
and composed woman
I have ever met.
For example...
Where are you staying tonight?
There are already
three women here.
It's not convenient
for me to stay, right?
I was not asking you to stay here.
What I mean is, you don't have to
go back to your place either.
It has already been smashed anyway.
Well,
alright then.
I'll just
find somewhere else to stay.
That is easy.
After this is settled,
I'll fix up your place properly.
And I'll thank
your female friend as well.
I'll get going, then.
Alright.
I am leaving.
Now that your dad
is not getting married,
shouldn't you celebrate?
Once this one is gone,
another one comes right after.
My dad is actually a good person.
He just keeps falling
for the wrong women.
What kind of problem is that?
If you say he is love-obsessed,
he can immediately fall for someone else
and chase after her like crazy.
It has left me with a shadow.
Whenever a man pursues me,
I think of my dad,
and I feel it's ridiculous.
So now,
I am always the one pursuing men.
And the colder a man is toward me,
the more I feel
it's strangely addictive.
Like someone like Mr. He Han.
How is He Han cold toward you?
Isn't he quite warm with you?
No.
He is only enthusiastic
when talking about you,
not about me.
But I am still happy.
As long as I can see him,
I feel happy.
Were you the one chasing him before?
No.
So, he chased you?
Not really.
Then, how did you two get together?
We argued.
We argued our way into it.
What kind of arguments?
Were they
playful arguments or real fights?
Real fights.
The kind that could blow the place up.
How did you make up after fighting?
Zhou Mei hasn't come back yet.
She asked me to
leave the door open for her.
So, how did you make up?
I forgot.
(Three Years Ago)
♪If the sky and the sea
turned upside down♪
Thanks.
You didn't take the trophy.
Wait.
Stop.
♪If back then we had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
Doesn't it work?
I am just not used to
seeing you so proper.
I am not used to your outfit either.
Wearing pants under a skirt.
What were you thinking?
- Seriously? Is it not something new?
- Who did you learn that from?
Just tell me if it looks good or not.
Next time you get me a suit,
can you make it a bit looser?
These pants are way too tight today.
♪This one eternal photograph♪
You wrote over
two million words in a year.
Finally got a trophy like this,
and I broke it.
It's fine. It's just a trophy.
If it's broken, it's fine.
We got the honor, right?
But the trophy matters, too.
Then, we will write another one.
Even if we do, it won't say
Outstanding Author of 2021 anymore.
Well, of course.
Next year would be 2022, right?
He Han, look.
Found it.
Is that a preserved egg?
Hey,
don't fall asleep.
I am not asleep.
Stop lying.
Wake up.
I heard it.
I was not snoring.
Then, who was snoring?
(He Han, The Desert Rises to Fame)
You are not sleepy, right?
No.
You are sleepy?
I am not.
How could I feel
sleepy when I am with you?
I am not disturbing your work, am I?
Not at all.
That is good.
You came back late tonight.
We even went to the police station.
Zhang Yousen got into a fight.
What about now?
Is he all right?
He is fine.
Why did he get into a fight?
Just a young man trying to show off.
Picking trouble for no reason.
Nice.
What are you doing?
Showing respect to a beauty.
Zhou Mei, you should go first.
Do you know
how awkward this is for me?
I am already in my thirties,
yet I still have to watch my boyfriend
rolling around
on the ground with a thug.
It's always like that.
You cannot just avoid it.
What about your other boyfriends?
What would they do
in a situation like this?
Why are you not going to sleep?
With a topic this interesting,
I would be wide awake.
My other boyfriends
wouldn't do something like this.
Look at you,
spending all night with Zhang Yousen
playing games until
dawn before coming back.
What are you trying to do?
Well, when you are in a relationship,
you have to do something
to pass the long nights.
If you go home right after dinner,
it kills the mood.
Going to a hotel or watching a movie...
I am not in the mood
for that with him yet.
Go to sleep.
(Zhanqiao: You are waiting
for Lawyer Bei to come find you.)
(May: He owes me an explanation.)
Hello, what is it?
Are you at home?
I want you to help buy
breakfast for my grandmother.
She cannot take her medicine
on an empty stomach.
The helper stopped coming.
I am on my way now.
Thank you.
Take care.
Min.
Grandma.
I am Ling Yikai's girlfriend.
My name is Zhao Lanxin.
I brought you breakfast.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Where is Min?
She has something to
take care of these days.
Ling Yikai asked me to come.
I brought you vegetable buns,
Shaomai,
wonton,
and soy milk.
Come, sit.
Which one would you like?
I won't eat.
I'll wait for Min.
Grandma,
it's like this.
I am staying next door now.
The helper has
something to handle these days,
so I am bringing your meals.
You have to take
these medicines after eating.
If you don't eat now,
it will be past the time to take them.
But...
I don't even know
what medicine I am taking.
Min always
prepared them for me.
Grandma,
it's all right.
I have checked and memorized everything.
Losartan potassium tablets,
metformin capsules,
and triamterene tablets.
Did I get them right?
I am so sorry.
Min didn't
inform us.
She just left on her own.
Actually, Mr. Ling, you know...
It's not easy to find a helper
for your grandmother.
Min left because
it's too dark here at night.
She could not settle in here,
so she left.
I understand.
I'll pay more.
Please help me find someone suitable.
Help me.
Please.
Grandma,
let me show you how
to recognize these pills.
Just in case you need
to take them yourself,
or someone else gives them to you,
you will at least know
what you are taking.
Alright.
Come.
Grandma, give me your hand.
Let's feel this capsule first.
This is the metformin capsule.
Can you feel
the shape of the capsule?
Alright.
Let's try another one.
This one.
Oval-shaped,
a little thicker.
This is the losartan potassium tablet.
Can you feel it?
There is another one that is similar.
Here, give me your hand.
This one is also oval-shaped.
Before the agency finds a new helper,
you can leave Grandma to me.
It will still take another week.
Aren't you going to work?
It's just one week.
I can take her with me to work.
Thank you.
I am leaving.
When you go to
the office later, and they ask,
think about what you are going to say.
It's fine.
Lawyer Bei already knows.
No idea who
was so quick to pass it on.
So, what did he say to you?
He asked about what happened.
I figured there was nothing
I couldn't tell him,
so I told him.
Who would have thought
that he thinks being in a relationship
is affecting my work.
He told me to weigh the pros and cons
and promise him
that work comes before love.
Otherwise,
he will reconsider whether I stay.
As your supervisor,
it's fair that he said something after
you ended up at the police station.
He has never really
been in a relationship.
Or rather,
he has never truly loved someone.
So he wouldn't understand.
When he married his wife,
it was because of her family background.
I told him
the fight was my responsibility.
It won't happen again.
But asking me to restrain my
relationship? It's not going to happen.
People may be able to stop many things,
but the one thing
they cannot stop is love.
Right?
Then,
what did he say?
He asked me
to pause my work
and take two days to write a reflection.
What is that?
Am I a school student?
Not allowed to date?
He can fire me if he wants,
but I am not writing any reflection.
If he really fires me,
I'll tell everyone at the firm
that I was dismissed
because I believe in love.
Pull over.
Alright.
I'll take a taxi back to the office.
You go back and write the reflection.
Submit it to Lawyer Bei
before the end of the day.
If you lose this job,
then we are done.
Do not feel pressured.
What I choose to do is my own decision.
It has nothing to do with you, Zhou Mei.
I am not joking.
Are you free at noon?
I want to see you.
I was about to find you
if you hadn't come to me.
You are not planning
to fire Zhang Yousen
over this, are you?
If he gets dismissed now, it'll be hard
for him to find another job later.
I am not going to fire Zhang Yousen.
But for his inappropriate behavior,
asking him to write a reflection
is part of company policy, right?
What if he refuses?
Then, I'll write it for him.
He is young and capable,
and he hasn't done
anything unforgivable.
Why would I fire him?
But...
But what?
I hope you
don't hold back his future.
I am holding back his future?
Do you know that now
he goes to work every day,
looking worn out?
With dark circles under his eyes,
he even dozes off during meetings.
It's already affecting the company.
And all of this
is because of you.
I plan
to transfer him
to the Southwest Branch.
What if he does not want to go?
After two years, he can come back
and apply for his license.
Then, he can take cases on his own
and build up his own clients.
In a few years,
he might even become
the youngest partner in the firm.
If it were me,
I would want that opportunity.
You are trying to send him away
because you are jealous, right?
I don't want you making use
of an innocent young man.
I have every reason to dismiss him,
but I believe
you wouldn't want to see that happen.
Many relationships begin
by accident,
in a moment of impulse.
If you have any issues with me,
take it out on me.
Do not drag innocent people into it.
That will only bring you more trouble.
What right do I have
to take issue with you?
Shouldn't everything
between us be pleasant?
We are the best gift
life has given each other.
Even if life is a mess,
having this gift
is still something to be glad about.
Then, don't let me
run into your wife again.
I know you are married.
I also know that it's your boundary.
So you don't need to say it to my face.
Doing that
only makes me feel you look down on me
or on what we have.
When I have gatherings with friends,
if my wife is free,
I bring her along.
Usually,
I don't get many chances
to have meals with her.
I am not always willing,
but...
sometimes, I feel
I should.
Let me tell you one more thing.
Your wife has probably noticed us.
Do not underestimate
a woman's intuition.
This time,
you made it worse.
So, I suggest
you don't send Zhang Yousen away.
Otherwise, your wife will think
it's because you are jealous.
I'll handle things with Zhang Yousen.
He shouldn't be dragged into this.
Since we both think he
is a good young man,
let's
protect him.
Mrs. Bei,
what a coincidence.
I came to see him about something.
The secretary said
he was dining here, so I came over.
I am here to speak to Lawyer Bei
on Zhang Yousen's behalf.
He made a small mistake.
Please give him another chance.
It won't happen again.
Another place setting, please.
Ma'am, your utensils.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
I didn't expect
you to care so much
about your boyfriend, Miss Zhou.
I thought someone like you
would have men
caring about you instead.
Whether someone cares is fate.
It has nothing to do with looks.
I have never had
an easy life.
Zhang Yousen is a good young man.
But forgive me for saying this,
Miss Zhou,
with your conditions,
you should find someone
better, someone who can take care of you
and let you
live without worry.
Right?
Alright then.
If there is a chance,
Mrs. Bei, please
introduce someone to me.
I'll find time
to speak to Zhang Yousen.
I hope you
will also remind him
to focus on his work
and not let play
delay what matters.
Alright.
Thank you, Lawyer Bei.
Please enjoy your meal.
I'll take my leave.
Excuse me, the bill.
No need. I'll pay.
You go ahead.
I asked for your help,
so I cannot let you pay.
It's fine.
At last night's Author Night,
the spotlight
belonged to Gu Yan.
But Lin Zhanqiao
belonged to He Han.
At a time like this, we,
especially you, should give it a push.
What is broken can come back together.
May I ask you something?
Ask as many as you like.
Earlier, when Zhiyuan withdrew
their investment from Lin Zhanqiao,
was it you or Zhao Lanxin
who tipped them off?
Look,
Zhiyuan already
made it clear.
Right?
It was just a coincidence.
They were eating there,
and someone at the next table
was talking about Lin Zhanqiao's
newly signed authors,
saying she could not pay them.
And it just so happened
you were at that table.
Well...
How would I know someone was listening?
So, all of this was your doing.
On one hand,
you shook the investor's
confidence in Lin Zhanqiao,
and on the other,
you had Zhao Lanxin intercept
new authors
Lin Zhanqiao hadn't paid yet.
And on your side,
you pretend to be so loyal
and ready to take over anytime.
I did all this because of you.
Because I know
you are worried
they might get back together,
right?
After all, you are new here.
If you don't want to eat, get out.
I eat.
(Dingqi Author Night ends,
lighting up Shanghai.)
Mantou,
is this true?
So, Mr. He Han is coming back?
Most likely.
When Ms. Lin comes later,
don't start gossiping.
Let her announce it herself.
After all that, they are back together.
Looks like wedding candy
is coming this time.
They should have
gotten married long ago.
It's not too late.
Had they married early,
they might have divorced early too.
But recently, I thought
our boss and Gu Yan were together.
Once you have seen the ocean,
no other water compares, you know?
Gu Yan left with our boss yesterday.
Why are there no photos of them?
Who knows?
Zhangzhu,
you are with our boss every day.
Any inside news?
I didn't notice anything.
Ms. Lin.
These are the updated drafts.
Has Gu Yan submitted his draft?
Not yet. I'll remind him now.
I'll go to him myself.
Okay.
The update is not ready yet?
I am writing it.
I'll send it to you later.
You don't need to come here.
Then, we will talk later.
I have a project meeting this afternoon.
After it ends, I'll come to you.
Lin Zhanqiao, He Han,
and I used to be colleagues.
So I saw their relationship
with my own eyes.
You wouldn't want He Han to come back
and work with Lin Zhanqiao again.
Emotionally,
they are old lovers,
reuniting after a long separation.
Their closeness will
definitely be stronger than before.
And accordingly,
the time she spends on you
will decrease.
Second,
for Dingqi,
publicity aside,
He Han is still more valuable than you.
Once you start competing
under the same company,
wherever you go,
you will still be
overshadowed by He Han.
You want to poach me?
Of course, you would say that.
I don't deny that I want to poach you.
Otherwise, why would I come to you?
But I am not trying to force you.
Nor do I expect that after hearing this,
you will lean toward me.
I have always
done better than I speak.
As long as you give me a chance,
I'll show you
what it means to value you
and what it means to see you as the
most important person in the company.
From nothing to something,
it was Lin Zhanqiao who
helped me find my worth.
At least for now,
I am still her most important author.
To be fair,
Lin Zhanqiao never really spent
that much time on you.
You have had it hard.
You are used to no one
managing you or caring about you.
So, when Lin Zhanqiao
gives you a little sweetness,
you think you have
gained the whole world.
Without comparison,
don't rush to conclusions.
I think things are already good now.
I trust Lin Zhanqiao.
I don't need comparisons.
I just don't want He Han's arrival
to change how things are now.
I am only telling you
that you deserve better.
I'll go now.
Otherwise, if Lin Zhanqiao comes
and sees me here with you,
you'll have an even
harder time explaining it.
Call me anytime.
Twenty-four hours a day.
Call me when you have no one to talk to.
Xiaolongbao. Enjoy.
Thank you.
Hello?
What are you doing?
Has Mr. Fan's contract been signed?
I have already
revised it and sent it over,
but he hasn't replied yet.
Did you chase him?
No.
That is right.
The more casual you seem now,
the better. Understand?
And you can even make the contract terms
a little tougher.
The harder you are to deal with,
the more determined
he will be to get it. Understand?
What are you doing tonight?
How about we go watch a movie
and give it a push?
Or we can just have dinner.
I happen to discuss with you.
Tonight, at the French restaurant
near Chenxing.
I'll book the table.
When the time comes, we split the bill.
Dinner is fine,
but no splitting the bill.
I am here to help you.
You should pay for the meal, right?
Fine.
See you tonight.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪